https://www.wideners.com/privacy-policy

Help
Search:
Search
Home
Privacy Policy
Personally Identifiable Information
To order from our website, you must provide us with some categories of information known as “Personally Identifiable Information” (“PII”).
If you create a customer account or begin the checkout process, we will request and collect the following PII: first and last name; credit card number; email address; billing and shipping address; and telephone number.
Depending on your state and the product you wish to order, we may also be required to request and collect a firearm owner identification card.
You can always edit your PII by entering your customer account and making your desired changes.
We understand your PII is sensitive.
We take the following measures to protect it.
We maintain compliance with the PCI-DSS guidelines established by the major credit card companies.
We secure our checkout process with strong encryption methods.
We limit disclosure of your PII to only those parties who are critically necessary to the function of our business.
Sharing Your Personally Identifiable Information
Aside from what is outlined below, we will not share any of your information with third parties, and third parties are not able to collect your PII when you use our site.
Here is who we share your PII with and why:
– Our credit card processing company to process your transaction efficiently and accurately;
– Our 3PL warehouse to pick and pack your order;
– Our common carriers to ship your package to your desired location;
– Our digital marketing partner to communicate with you about your order and our business;
– Our back-end support staff to serve you and make our business run smooth.
We also reserve the right to share your PII in the following circumstances:
– If we receive a valid legal request from a court or government agency;
– If we believe in good faith that sharing your PII is necessary to protect ourselves, our business, or members of the public;
– If we believe in good faith that sharing your PII is necessary to enforce our Shipping and Other Policies.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
In addition to PII, we also collect some categories of Non-Personally Identifiable Information: device information, operating system, IP address, and browser type.
Also, like most ecommerce websites, we uses cookies. We use first-party and third-party cookies in combination with Google Analytics and Advertising Features to help us improve your experience on our site, including offering better products and making browsing and ordering much easier. These cookies are linked directly to our site, and we do not share them with any additional third parties. They collect demographics and interests-based data as well as data like browser, referring site, and the details of site visits. Zero PII is linked with these cookies. All data collected is anonymous. For more information, and to see the additional terms to which you are agreeing by using our site, check out Google Analytics Terms of Service linked here.
Also, you can avoid Google Analytics data collection by modifying your Google Ad Preferences settings, or by using Google’s opt-out add-on for your browser (you can find it here).
Notice to Nevada Customers
To submit a request under NRS 603A for us to not sell your PII, please email privacy@wideners.com.
Staying In Touch
Whenever changes are made to this Privacy Policy, a revised version will be posted here.
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to either email us at wideners@wideners.com or call 1-800-615-3006.
Shop by Category
Handgun Ammo10mm Ammo25 ACP Ammo32 Ammo357 Magnum Ammo357 Sig Ammo38 S&W Ammo38 Special Ammo38 Super Ammo380 Ammo40 Cal Ammo44 Magnum Ammo44 Special Ammo45 ACP Ammo45 GAP Ammo45 Long Colt Ammo50 AE Ammo7.62 Nagant Ammo7.62x25 Ammo9mm Ammo9x18 Ammo (Makarov)Rifle Ammo17 Hornet Ammo204 Ruger Ammo22 Hornet Ammo222 Ammo22-250 Ammo223 (5.56) Ammo243 Ammo25-06 Ammo25-20 WINCHESTER260 REMINGTON270 Ammo30 Carbine Ammo300 Blackout Ammo300 Win Mag Ammo30-06 Ammo303 British Ammo30-30 Ammo308 Ammo338 Lapua Ammo350 Legend Ammo375 H&H Magnum Ammo44-40 Ammo45-70 Ammo5.45x39 Ammo5.7x28mm Ammo50 Cal Ammo6.5 Creedmoor Ammo6.5 Grendel Ammo6.5x52mm Carcano Ammo6.5 Swedish Ammo6.8 SPC Ammo7.5x55 Swiss Ammo7.62x39 Ammo7.62x54r Ammo7.92X33 KURZ Ammo7mm-08 Ammo7mm Rem Mag Ammo7mm Mauser Ammo8mm Mauser Ammo8x56 RS Männlicher Ammo9.3x62mm Mauser AmmoRimfire Ammo22 Win Auto Ammo22LR Ammo22 Magnum Ammo22 Short Ammo22 WRF Ammo17 HMR Ammo17 WSM AmmoShotgun Ammo12 Gauge Ammo20 Gauge Ammo410 AmmoReloading SuppliesBulletsRifle Bullets17 Hornet Bullets204 Ruger Bullets22 Hornet Bullets22 Savage High Power Bullets222 Bullets223 Bullets (.224 diameter)243 Bullets25 Caliber (25-06) Bullets257 Weatherby Bullets270 Bullets30 Carbine Bullets300 Blackout Bullets300 Savage Bullets303 Caliber Bullets (303 British)30-30 Bullets308 Bullets.338 Bullets348 Bullets358 Bullets375 Bullets405 Win Bullets416 Rem Mag Bullets44-40 Bullets.452 Bullets / 450 Bushmaster450/400 Nitro Bullets45-70 Bullets458 Lott Bullets458 SOCOM Bullets458 Win Mag Bullets470 Nitro Bullets475 Linebaugh Bullets5.6x52R Bullets50 BMG Bullets500 Nitro Express Bullets6.5mm Bullets (.264)6.5 Carcano Bullets6mm Bullets7.7 Jap Bullets7.62x39 Bullets7mm Bullets7mm Mag Bullets7mm Mauser Bullets7mm-08 Bullets8mm Bullets9.3mm BulletsPistol Bullets45 Long Colt Bullets454 Casull Bullets10mm Bullets25 Auto Bullets30 Cal Bullets32 Auto Bullets32 Special Bullets327 Federal Mag Bullets357 Magnum Bullets357 Sig Bullets38 Special Bullets38 Super Bullets380 Bullets40 Cal Bullets41 Magnum Bullets44 Magnum Bullets44 Special Bullets45 ACP Bullets45 GAP Bullets50 AE Bullets500 S&W Bullets9mm Bullets9mm Makarov BulletsShop By Bullet BrandArmscor BulletsBarnes BulletsBerger BulletsBerry's BulletsHornady BulletsMaster Match BulletsNosler BulletsRemington BulletsSierra BulletsSpeer BulletsSurplus BulletsBrass Casings44 Magnum Brass Casings10mm Brass Casings223 Rem Brass Casings243 Win Brass Casings270 Winchester Brass Casings300 Blackout Brass Casings308 Win / 7.62x51mm Brass Casings338 Lapua Brass Casings357 Magnum Brass Casings357 Sig Brass Casings38 Special Brass Casings380 Auto Brass Casings40 S&W Brass Casings45 ACP Brass Casings45 Colt Brass Casings50 BMG Brass Casings5.56 Brass Casings6.5 Creedmoor Brass Casings6.5 Grendel Brass Casings6.5 Norma Brass Casings9mm Brass CasingsShooting AccessoriesAmmo CansTargetsFirearm CleaningEye & Ear ProtectionHolstersGun Cases & Gun StorageGun SafesMagazines & Mag LoadersMagpul MagazinesGlock MagazinesMec-Gar MagazinesD&H MagazinesAdditional MagazinesMagazine LoadersMagazine AccessoriesGift Cards
Receive Widener’s E-Blast!
Get the latest news and updates
Notifications for Special Deals!
Other great deals, and information!
Fax: (423) 815-1348 (24 Hours/Day)
© 2020 Wideners.com. All Rights Reserved.
